JOLLIBEER D. REJUSO

9080RE Sitio Little Batangas St. Brgy. Ibabang Polo, Pagbilao Quezon +63 968 853 4514 jollibeerrejuso@gmail.com



JOB OBJECTIVES

To be part of a well-organized company where I can share my knowledge and skills for the Company's growth, while giving a good opportunity for me to further enhance my skills and experience for my career growth and future success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Test Technician

Allegro Microsystems Philippines Inc. June 2019 - October 2022

JOB SUMMARY

Performs electrical, mechanical, or software troubleshooting to determine problems in nonfunctioning test Equipment. Dismantles, adjusts, repairs, and assembles equipment according to layout plans, blueprints, operating or repair manuals, and/or rough sketches or drawings. Uses tests and diagnostic equipment to perform checkouts. May perform equipment modifications as directed by test/manufacturing engineers.

KEY JOB RESPOSIBILITIES

- ✓ Exemplify implementation of accountability, discipline, moral conduct, and 5S.
- ✓ Initiates the communication of all machine issues and concerns affecting equipment efficiency and performance to engineers. Provide necessary technical data to ensure that responsible engineers can give proper dispositions.
- ✓ Follows the standard operating procedures. Logs consistently all repair activities done for all machines.
- ✓ Assist in making systematic analysis of line issues, analyze root cause and implement activities to eliminate top recurring problems. Collaborate with other departments to reduce downtime.
- ✓ Collaborate with peers to achieve department goals and company goals. Contributes ideas for continuous improvement.
- ✓ Performs other related duties that the immediate or next immediate supervisor may assign.
- ✓ Conduct tester Preventive Maintenance and Calibration, GR&R data generation, and analysis according to company standard procedures.
- ✓ In-charge of resolving standard level test system performance issues in the line
- ✓ Capable of debugging test programs and recommend test program revisions.
- ✓ Performs TPE standard operating procedures.
- ✓ Provide Failure Analysis Report

Test Equipment Technician

Allegro Microsystems Philippines Inc. July 2014 – June 2019

JOB SUMMARY

Execute repairs and maintenance activities of Test Center equipment per line to achieve 95% uptime or better, meet machine's rated speed or capability, and produce defect-free products at a minimal cost.

KEY JOB RESPOSIBILITIES

- ✓ Executes daily and weekly maintenance activities.
- ✓ Implement corrective actions to quality and machine performance-related issues and Provide feedback.
- ✓ Performs repairs and maintenance on equipment, including preventive/predictive maintenance activities.
- ✓ Maintain 5S in all areas.

- ✓ Provide technical support to the production line.
- ✓ Reports consistently all repair activities done for all machines.
- ✓ Provides technical information to maintenance-related problems in production.
- ✓ Informs remaining spare parts on hand.
- ✓ Follows the standard operating procedures.
- ✓ Reports issues and concerns were affecting machine uptime and the quality of the product.
- ✓ Keep tools and instruments in good condition.
- ✓ Contributes ideas for continuous improvement.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Bachelor of Science in Electronics and Communications Engineering (ETEEAP PROGRAM)
Manuel S. Enverga University Foundations
2020-2021

Diploma in Electronics and Communications Engineering Technology (ECE-Ladderize) Rizal Technological University 2011-2014

SKILLS

- ✓ Capable to read and interpret Electronics Schematic and Diagrams
- ✓ Proficiency in the use of hand tools, measuring tools and test equipment
- ✓ Experience in setup debugging and test methodologist
- ✓ Demonstrable knowledge of pneumatic and electro-mechanical system
- ✓ Solid knowledge in preventive maintenance and troubleshooting on Automatic Test Equipment such as, RASCO SO2000, Multi-Test 85 Series, MCT, Janus and Eagle Test System
- ✓ Computer literacy, knowledge in MS Office, Galaxy Examinator, Camstar and Shell

LEADERSHIP

✓ Cluster Line Leader

- Disseminate task to cluster members to ensure the prioritization of activities and expedited task
- Provide updates and reports about the line situation to the immediate Superior
- Provide reports on the current manpower attendance, concern and issues.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthday: December 31, 1990

Weight: 135 lbs. **Height:** 165 cm.

Religion: Roman Catholic

Ethnicity: Asian

Dialect Spoken: English/Tagalog **Dialect Written:** English/Tagalog

Civil Status: Single